Finding Aid for John Engler Papers, 1968-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Gubernatorial Papers, 1970-2003; 411 linear feet
  - Office of the First Lady, Michelle Engler, 1990-2002; 17.4 linear feet
    - Boards, 1991-2002; 3.6 linear feet
      - Michigan Community Service Commission, 1991-2002; 2 linear feet
        - 1998
          - Americorps, 1998 (Box 408)
          - Letter honoring Dr. Michael Tate, June 23, 1998 (Box 408)
          - ConnectMichigan Campaign for Volunteerism Booklets, September 1998 (Box 408)
          - Meeting, September 11, 1998 (Box 408)
          - Meeting at CS Mott Foundation, September 11, 1998 (Box 408)
          - Phone Call, November 30, 1998 (Box 408)
          - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 408)
        - 1999
          - Letters/Quotes Michelle Engler, 1999 (Box 408)
          - Plan for Development and Transition, January 10, 1999 (Box 408)
          - AmeriCorps, February 19, 1999 (Box 408)
          - Executive Committee Conference Call, March 11, 1999 (Box 408)
          - Background information for meeting with Harris Wofford, April 1999 (Box 408)
            (CEO of the Corporation for National Service)
          - Retreat, July 1999 (Box 408)
          - Retreat, Mackinac Is, September 24-25, 1999 (Box 408)
          - Michigan Reading Readiness Corps, September 29, 1999 (Box 408)
          - Make A Difference Day, October 23, 1999 (Box 408)
          - Executive Directors' Report, November 8, 1999 (Box 408)
        - 2000
          - Michelle Engler Letters: SuperCon 2000 Annual Report, MADD, 2000 (Box 408)
          - 2000 Governors' Service Awards Nomination form packets, January13 2000 (Box 408)
          - Commission Meeting, January 21, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Jennifer Granholm Project, January 24, 2000 (Box 408)
            (2000 for 2000 Michigan's Mentoring Initiative)
          - Mandated Community Service: Rep. Kukuk's office, February 2000 (Box 408)
          - President's Service Awards, February 1, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Governor's Service Award nominations, February 14, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Executive Committee Meeting, March 24, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Commission Meeting, May 10, 2000; 2 folders (Box 408)
          - Kyle Caldwell's Letter to Peter Hoekstra, May 15, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Drafts of Governor's Service Award letters, May 18, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Russ Mawby letter to Michelle Engler, June 13, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Retreat, July 26, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Make a Difference Letter, August 2000 (Box 408)
          - Executive Committee Meeting, August 11, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Russ Mawby Press Release, August 14, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Director's Report, September 13, 2000 (Box 408)
          - PowerUP/Sen. Spence Abraham, September 20, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Executive Committee Meeting, November 17, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Commission Meeting, Detroit, December 8, 2000; 2 folders (Box 408)
          - Engler Family Fund, December 19, 2000 (Box 408)
          - Governor's Service Awards Forms, 2001; December 2000 (Box 408)
        - 2001
          - Notes/memos from Kyle Caldwell, 2001 (Box 408)
          - American Association of State Service Commissions White Paper, January 30, 2001 (Box 408)
          - Commission Meeting, February 9, 2001 (Box 408)
          - Executive Committee Conference Call, April 20, 2001 (Box 409)
          - Executive Committee Conference Call, August 17, 2001 (Box 409)
          - Board Retreat, September 10-11, 2001 (Box 409)
          - Americorps: Kyle Caldwell/Spence Abraham Correspondence, October 16, 2001 (Box 409)
        - 2002
          - 10th Anniversary Celebration, February 12, 2002; 2 folders (Box 409)
          - Meeting with Legislators, Lansing, February 12, 2002 (Box 409)
      - Michigan Nonprofit Association, 1997-2002; 0.1 linear feet
        - Michigan Nonprofit Association, 1997 (Box 409)
        - Michigan Nonprofit Association, 1998-1999 (Box 409)
        - Yearbook, 2000 (Box 409)
        - Guide to Michigan Nonprofit Association's Policy Concerns and Recommendations, 2001-2002 (Box 409)
      - National Commission on Service Learning, 2000-2002; 0.4 linear feet
        - Thomas Jefferson Forum, Inc., Boston, MA, 1991 (Box 409)
        - Initial Appointment Information, November 2000 (Box 409)
        - National Commission on Service Learning, December 5-6, 2000 (Box 409)
        - Service Learning Opening Session, December 5, 2000 (Box 409)
        - Service Learning Afternoon Session, December 5, 2000 (Box 409)
        - Service Learning, December6, 2000 (Box 409)
        - Site Visit, Dewey Center, March 27, 2001 (Box 409)
        - Meeting, Denver, Colorado, April 3-4, 2001; 3 folders (Box 409)
        - Briefing Papers, April 3, 2001 (Box 409)
        - Resource Materials, April 3, 2001 (Box 409)
        - News Clips, April 3, 2001 (Box 409)
        - Membership Organization Academy for Educational Development, May 2001 (Box 409)
        - Work Group Conference Call, May 30, 2001 (Box 409)
        - Meeting, Washington, DC, January 29-30, 2002 (Box 409)
      - Points of Light Foundation, Washington, DC, 1995-2002; 0.4 linear feet
        - Article on Governor George Romney, 1995 (Box 409)
        - Letter re: Michelle's appointment, December 27, 1995 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, Plano, Texas, January 18, 1996 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, March 7, 1996 (Box 409)
        - General Information, 1997 (Box 409)
        - Board Meetings, December 1, 1997 (Box 409)
        - Governmental Affairs Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 409)
        - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, Anaheim, California, February 5-6, 1998 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, Washington, DC, June 8, 1998 (Box 409)
        - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 409)
        - Board of Directors Information, January 11, 1999 (Box 409)
        - Michelle Engler letter to Bob Goodwin, RSVP Award, March 22, 1999 (Box 409)
        - Communications Committee, April 15, 1999 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, May 16, 1999 (Box 409)
        - Congressman Peter Hoekstra letter Wofford/Goodwin responses, July 1999 (Box 409)
        - Board Report, August 1999 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, Kennebunkport, Maine, September 12, 1999 (Box 409)
        - Kennebunkport Event, September 12-13, 1999 (Box 409)
        - Board Retreat, February 11-12, 2000 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, Washington, DC, May 16, 2000 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, Washington, DC, September 18, 2000 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, George Bush Presidential Library, College Station, Texas, February 23-24, 2001 (Box 409)
        - Board Meeting, Washington, DC, May 21, 2001 (Box 409)
        - Congressional Visits, June 13, 2002 (Box 409)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations and Projects, 1991-2002; 1 linear feet
      - 1994 Michigan International Year of the Family, 1994 (Box 410)
      - 1994 Michigan International Year of the Family: Resolution No. 574, 1994 (Box 410)
      - 2001 Arvon Woman of Achievement Award, 2001 (Box 410)
      - American Governors' Mansions, 1996-1998 (Box 410)
      - "Art & the Law" Exhibit at Kresge, September 1996 (Box 410)
      - Artrain/Points of Light Information Correspondence, 1991 (Box 410)
      - Artrain USA, 1991 (Box 410)
      - Big Brothers/Big Sisters of America, April 18, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Boys Hope/Girls Hope Detroit, 2000 (Box 410)
      - Breast Cancer Awareness, 1994 (Box 410)
      - Caring Arms Task Force Lt. Governor, 1992 (Box 410)
      - Caring Program for Children, 1994 (Box 410)
      - Children's Trust Fund Information, 1991-1993 (Box 410)
      - Christian Home Educators' Support System: Mrs. Amy Lyzenga, April 3, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Community in Schools (CIS) Chicago/Houston, April 1, 1999 (Box 410)
      - Corporation for National Service:, February 19, 2002 (Box 410)
      - Corporation for National Service Reauthorization/Act of, 1993 (Box 410)
      - Corporation for National Service: Transition, 2000 (Box 410)
      - Council of Michigan Foundations: Learning to Give project, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Detroit Public Library, November 30, 1992 (Box 410)
      - Dove Foundation, October 4, 1999 (Box 410)
      - Faith and Community Based Initiative Follow-up Meeting, May 10, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Focus: Hope, October 1997 (Box 410)
      - Focus: Hope, September 2001 (Box 410)
      - Food Bank Council of Michigan (Draft Letter for Large Donors), 2001 (Box 410)
      - Fowler Center: Michelle Engler Honorary Chair Capital Campaign, August 2000 (Box 410)
      - Girlstown Auction, November 9, 1991 (Box 410)
      - Girlstown Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 410)
      - Giving Tree Farm, 1991-1993 (Box 410)
      - Giving Tree Farm, 1997 (Box 410)
      - Gleaner's Community Food Bank of Greater Detroit, 2000 (Box 410)
      - Gleaner's Correspondence, 1999 (Box 410)
      - Grand Rapids Griffins Youth Foundation, 1996 (Box 410)
      - Grocers' Association/Food Aid: Michelle Engler's Solicitation Letter for FoodAid, January 15, 1992 (Box 410)
      - Habitat for Humanity International Women's Build, February 13, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Habitat for Humanity: Ken Benson letter to Governor and Michelle Engler, June 4, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Habitat for Humanity (Mason County) Ludington, Michigan, June 4, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Habitat for Humanity: Michelle Engler letter to new "homeowners,", May 26, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Habitat for Humanity (Saginaw, MI), June 8, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Hispanic Issues, June 17, 1998 (Box 410)
      - Hospice of Michigan, April 24, 2000 (Box 410)
      - Immunization Meeting, January 10, 1992 (Box 410)
      - Immunization, September 30, 1997 (Box 410)
      - Impression 5 Science Museum, 1991 (Box 410)
      - Karmanos Cancer Institute, May 8, 2000 (Box 410)
      - K-Mart Women's Healthcare Classic, July 22, 1996 (Box 410)
      - Michigan Arts Plan, January 1993 (Box 410)
      - Michigan Cares, 1997 (Box 410)
      - Michigan Communities in Schools, September 4, 1998 (Box 410)
      - Michigan Harvest Gathering, 1998 (Box 410)
      - Michigan Historical Museum Board of Trustees, 1991-1992 (Box 410)
      - Michigan Library Association Roundtable, April 2, 1992 (Box 410)
      - Michigan State Medical Society Greetings Letter, October 6, 1993 (Box 410)
      - Michigan Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Alliance, 2000 (Box 410)
      - Miss Michigan, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Mother's Day Mammogram, 1999 (Box 410)
      - National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism: Michelle Engler Honorary Member of Leadership Committee, October 20, 1994 (Box 410)
      - Oxford Foundation: Porteous Book, 2000 (Box 410)
      - Salt Lake City 2002 Olympic Torch Relay, October 16, 2001, 2001-2002 (Box 410)
      - Tree of Hope: Kelly Rossman Meeting, June 8, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Tree of Hope Meeting, October 16, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Tree of Hope: Michelle Engler Quote, March 22, 2001 (Box 410)
      - Triplet Information Folder, 1999-2000 (Box 410)
      - Very Special ARTS-General File, 1992-1994 (Box 410)
      - Volunteerism, 1997 (Box 410)
      - Welfare Reform (First Term), 1992-1993 (Box 410)
      - White House Christmas Ornament, December 5, 2001 (Box 410)
      - WK Kellogg Foundation Literacy Grant Literacy Volunteers of Michigan Foundation, September 1, 1992 (Box 410)
      - Women's Leadership Network, 1992-1993 (Box 410)
      - Year of Women's Health '97 Public Relations, 1997 (Box 410)
    - Correspondence, 1991-2002; 1 linear feet
      - Patrice Merritt-Personal, 1990 (Box 411)
      - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 411)
      - Greater Lansing Catholic Education Foundation, December 5, 1991 (Box 411)
      - Correspondence, 1992; 2 folders (Box 411)
      - Michelle Engler Greeting Letter Lathrop Village Women's Club, February 6, 1992 (Box 411)
      - Jackson Child Care Center, October 8, 1992 (Box 411)
      - Editor Midland Daily News-Sharing Tree/Armory Day, December 21, 1992 (Box 411)
      - Correspondence, 1993; 2 folders (Box 411)
      - Congratulatory letters to Michelle Engler on going back to work, 1993 (Box 411)
      - Race for the Cure Thank You Letter to Michelle Engler, April 28, 1993 (Box 411)
      - Correspondence, 1994; 2 folders (Box 411)
      - Michelle Engler's Birthday Invite for Governor's Birthday Bash, October 1994 (Box 411)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 411)
      - Letters received from Triplet mothers, 1995 (Box 411)
      - Engler Thank-you notes for cards and letters received for birth of the triplets, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 411)
      - Correspondence, 1996; 2 folders (Box 411)
        (Correspondence 1997 is missing)
      - Correspondence, 1998; 2 folders (Box 411)
      - Oakwood Healthcare, 1998 (Box 411)
      - Correspondence, 1999-2002; 4 folders (Box 411)
    - Events, 1991-2002; 7 linear feet
      - 1991
        - Second Annual Math and Science Conference, February 1991 (Box 412)
        - St. Mary's School, Williamston, March 1991 (Box 412)
        - Holbrook Elementary School, March 1991 (Box 412)
        - Laingsburg Elementary School, March 18, 1994 (Box 412)
        - Wellston Elementary School, April 1991 (Box 412)
        - West Bloomfield School, April 1991 (Box 412)
        - Irwin Elementary School, April 1991 (Box 412)
        - Schavey Elementary, April 10, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Lewton Elementary, April 10, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Lapeer Elementary School, April 23, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Kalamazoo Voluntary Action Center Breakfast, April 24, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Celebration of Reading, Rockford, April 25, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Eastwood School--Partnership/Michcon, April 29, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Ionia County Literacy Council, April 29, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Lad & Lassie Preschool, Lansing, May 1991 (Box 412)
        - Parkview Elementary School, May 1991 (Box 412)
        - "Hats off to the first lady" Event, Ann Arbor, Michigan, May 8, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Clean-up, Fix-up Parade in Dearborn, May 9, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Gladwin Pines Nursing Home, May 13, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Holocaust Commemoration, May 14, 1991 (Box 412)
        - State Supreme Court Justices Reception, June 1991 (Box 412)
        - Clare/Gladwin Literacy Council, June 10, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Michigan Women's Foundation Gala, June 11, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Allison Degrow Tea Party, July 1991 (Box 412)
        - Meeting with Rep. Jacobetti re: Book Distribution Program, July 10, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Ford Education, Development and Training Center, July 18, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Genesee County Republican Womens Club, September 11, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Associations in Service to Michigan Recognition Dinner, September 24, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Historical Museum Meeting, September 27, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Red Cross Reception--Residence, October 2, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Birmingham Republican Women's Club, October 15, 1991 (Box 412)
        - FACT, Considine Center, Detroit, October 16, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Greater Lansing Catholic Education Foundation, October 23, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Food Bank Visit, Grand Rapids, October 28, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Republican Governor's Association-Dinner with President Bush, October 29, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Food Bank Visit, Battle Creek, October 20, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Food Bank Visit, Ishpeming, October 31, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Southwest Independent School District, San Antonio, November 1991 (Box 412)
        - Concerned Citizens for the Arts, November 4, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Genesee Food Bank, Flint, November 5, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Apples for Students, November 6, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Food Bank Visit, Lansing, November 7, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Michigan Historical Center Foundation Meeting, November 7, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Michigan Harvest Gathering, November 8, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Playmate Cooperative Nursery School, November 11, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Central Michigan University Breakfast, November 12, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Food Bank Visit, Detroit, November 13, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Michigan Harvest Gathering, November 13, 1991 (Box 412)
        - 32nd Annual Meeting Bloomfield Women's Club Luncheon, November 13, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Siersma Elementary School, Warren, November 13, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Orchard View Elementary School, November 14, 1991 (Box 412)
        - SHARE Program, November 14, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Fox Elementary School, November 20, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Bloomfield Hills High School, November 20, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Utah Information, November 26, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Greater Lansing Catholic Education Foundation, December 2, 1991 (Box 412)
        - Greater Lansing Food Bank Cristo Rey Center, December 3, 1991 (Box 412)
      - 1992
        - Billboard News Conference Michigan Harvest Gathering, January 7, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Eastover School Visit, Bloomfield Hills, January 8, 1992 (Box 412)
        - RSVP Fair, January 10, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Willow Elementary School Visit, Lansing, Michigan, January 21, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Shiawassee Adult Literacy, January 20, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Livingston County Literacy, January 22, 1992 (Box 412)
        - National Governors Association General Information, February 1-4, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Scouting for Food Luncheon, February 10, 1992 (Box 412)
        - General Federation of Women's Clubs Events, February 13, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Hinks School Visit, Alpena, February 1992 (Box 412)
        - Republican Women's Forum, February 18, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Lincoln Day, Shiawassee County, February 12, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Republican Women's Forum, February 18, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Northwest Elementary, February 21, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Upper Peninsula Visit, February 25, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Sault Area Chamber Banquet, February 26, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Upper Peninsula Visit, February 26, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Very Special Arts, February 28, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Math & Science, 6th Grade Girls Conference, February 29, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Brookwood Community, March 1992 (Box 412)
        - Food Aid Shopping Sweep, April 1, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Scouting for Food, April 1992 (Box 412)
        - Cellists Reception, April 4, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Food Aid Shopping Sweep, April 7, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Hillsdale Lincoln Day, April 9, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Breast Cancer Summit, April 10, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Bush Fundraiser, April 14, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Southwest Region Women Lawyers Association Luncheon Meeting, April 16, 1992 (Box 412)
        - McBryde Fundraiser, April 20, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Charlotte Adult Education, April 21, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Greater Lansing Adventist School, April 23, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Intergenerational Community Center, April 23, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Republican Women's Federation of Michigan, April 24, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Youth Summit, April 28, 1992 (Box 412)
        - Ionia County Lincoln Day Dinner, April 15, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Midland County Volunteer Action Center Event, April 28, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Southwest Michigan Republican Women, South Haven, May 11, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Europe Trip, May 13, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Very Special Arts, Greetings, Dennis Grantz, May 15, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Talon, Inc., Detroit, May 21, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Dorothy Comstock Riley Fund, May 27, 1992 (Box 413)
        - LPGA Reception, May 28, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Monroe Republican Women's Club, May 28, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Elmer Knopf Learning Center Graduation Ceremonies, June 2, 1992 (Box 413)
        - House Republican Fundraiser Breakfast, July 17, 1992 (Box 413)
        - National Governors' Association Meeting, August 1992 (Box 413)
        - GOP Convention, August 1992 (Box 413)
        - Victory '92 Luncheon Soave Residence, September 16, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Michigan Lawyers Auxiliary Luncheon, September 17, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Service Learning Conference, September 22, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Paula Zelenko Fundraiser, September 23, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Republican National Hispanic Fundraiser, September 24, 1992 (Box 413)
        - President and Mrs. Bush Whistle Stop Train Tour, September 25-27, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Evening on the Orient Express, October 5, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Peter Lund Event St. Clair Shores Senior Activities Center, October 6, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Al Kukuk for State Representative Event, October 6, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Hulsing Elementary School Visit, October 7, 1992 (Box 413)
        - State Rep. Lyn Bankes, October 7, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Mike McCulloch Fundraiser, October 7, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Mark Ouimet Fundraiser, October 7, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Michigan Harvest Gathering Kickoff, October 8, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Dorothy Bush-Koch Campaign for Bush-Quayle, October 8, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Economic Club of Macomb County, October 9, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Harwood Elementary School, Sterling Heights, October 9, 1992 (Box 413)
        - National Association Career Women Event, October 14, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Capital Area Literacy Coalition Day, Michelle Engler reading stories, October 14, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Barbara Bush, October 15, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Governor's Birthday Bash, October 1992 (Box 413)
        - Fundraiser for Doug Thomas, October 16, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Bev Hammerstrom Fundraiser, October 16, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Very Special Arts Program, October 18, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Presidential Debate, October 19, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Literacy Volunteers of America-Capital Area Literacy Coalition, October 20, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Michigan Women's Hall of Fame Event, October 22, 1992 (Box 413)
        - National Farm and Garden Assn. Annual Luncheon, October 22, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Event for Allen Lowe, October 23, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Shannon Brower Fundraiser, October 24, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Michelle McManus Event, October 25, 1992 (Box 413)
        - All Saints High School Visit, Bay City, October 28, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Mike Goshka Fundraiser, October 28, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Visit to Davison High School with Sandy Hill, October 28, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Presidential Visit, Detroit, October 29, 1992 (Box 413)
        - House Republican Fundraisers, Fall 1992 (Box 413)
        - Washington, DC Trip, November 5, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Council of Michigan Foundations Luncheon, November 5, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Extending a Hand Campaign PSA Shoot, November 10, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Harvest Gathering, Battle Creek, November 10, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Harvest Gathering Closing Ceremony, November 18, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Capitol Rededication, November 19, 1992 (Box 413)
        - St. Anne's Capital Campaign Committee, November 20, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Visit to Camp David, November 21-22, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Hob Nobble Gobble, November 25, 1992 (Box 413)
        - Take Pride in America Program, December 1992 (Box 413)
        - KISS Coalition "Phantom of the Opera,", 1992 (Box 413)
      - 1993
        - Editorial: "Be Somebody. Be a volunteer,", 1993 (Box 413)
        - Northwood University, 1993 (Box 413)
        - Children's Trust Fund Awards Ceremony, January 12, 1993 (Box 413)
        - City Year Meeting, Grand Rapids, January 12, 1993 (Box 413)
        - Meeting with Vernice Davis-Anthony re: Pediatric AIDS, January 12, 1993 (Box 413)
        - Meeting with Stephanie Comai-Page re: Communities First, January 12, 1993 (Box 413)
        - Service Learning and Education Reform "Conversation,", January 14, 1993 (Box 413)
        - Grantees Meeting, January 15, 1993 (Box 413)